<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Firciok</string>
    <!--    SHA-1-->
    <string name="default_web_client_id" translatable="false">657334798389-ncjhqbait1vfln5h2t9nu39v61epfq4g.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <!--    On Boarding-->
    <string name="OB_Title">Welcome</string>
    <string name="OB_Title_Desc">Step into a world of botanical beauty and artistic inspiration. Whether you are here to explore unique Van Gogh-inspired bouquets, shop for your favorite plants, or join us in our mission to plant trees, we are thrilled to have you. Your journey with us goes beyond shopping; it is a celebration of nature, creativity, and sustainable living</string>
    <string name="TC1">The following are the terms of use that govern the use of the Site (“Terms of Use”). By using the Site you expressly agree to be bound by these Terms of Use and the plantshop.me privacy policy and to follow these Terms of Use and all applicable laws and regulations governing the use of the Site. plantshop.me reserves the right to change these Terms of Use at any time, effective immediately upon posting on the Site. Please check this page of the Site periodically. We will note when there are updates to the Terms of Use at the bottom of the Terms of Use.</string>
    <string name="TC2">may terminate the privileges of any user who uses this Site to unlawfully transmit copyrighted material without a license, express consent, valid defense or fair use exemption to do so. If you submit information to this Site, you warrant that the information does not infringe the copyrights or other rights of third parties.</string>
    <string name="TC3">This Site may not be used by you for any commercial purposes such as to conduct sales of merchandise or services of any kind. You must obtain plantshop.me prior written consent to make commercial offers of any kind on the Site, whether by advertising, solicitations, links, or any other form of communication. plantshop.me will investigate and take appropriate legal action against anyone who violates this provision, including without limitation, removing the offending communication from the Site and barring such violators from use of the Site.</string>
    <string name="TC4">You agree that you are only authorized to visit, view and to retain a copy of pages of this Site for your own personal use, that you shall not duplicate, download, publish, modify or otherwise distribute the material on this Site for any purpose other than for personal use, unless otherwise specifically authorized by plantshop.me to do so. You also agree not to deep-link to the site for any purpose, unless specifically authorized by plantshop.me to do so. The content and software on this Site is the property of plantshop.me The cardholder must retain a copy of transaction records and Merchant policies and rules.</string>
</resources>